Marc Lester Lagunday

Full Stack Web Developer

Marcelo Green, Paranaque, Metro Manila 09565102662 marclesterlagunday@gmail.com

Self-motivated professional with 3 years of experience working on multiple projects. I enjoy creating things that live on the internet, whether that be website, applications, or anything in between. My goal is to contribute to a positive work environment while learning and applying work expectations.

As a full stack web developer, I love bridging the gap between engineering and design – combining my technical knowledge with keen for creating systems and design to create a beautiful product using the industries best practices.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Generika Drugstore (An Ayala Company)

Web Developer October 2019 – Present Projects:

- 1.) Generika Website develop and maintained the content of the website
- 2.) Generika Web Portal develop and migrated to a new platform with a team of developers
- 3.) API Development development of different API's for the inventory, transactions, authentication, and balance inquiry for existing systems in the company.

Vertere Global Solutions Inc - United Laboratories Inc. (UNILAB)

PHP Developer March 2018 – September 2019 Projects:

- 1.) Solmux Brand Website develop frontend and backend from scratch with a team using an MVC framework
- 2.) Ceelin Brand Website develop frontend and backend from scratch using an MVC framework
- 3.) Suppliers Audit Management System continued the development of backend and API's that is integrated with a mobile app
- 4.) Standard Content Management System develop a starter backend for all incoming projects that has modules ready for faster development, standard functionalities and standard web structure. Built and designed with the team of developers.

Airspeed Philippines Inc.

Web Development Intern October 2016 – March 2017 Projects:

- 1.) Speedregalo E-commerce website enhancement, maintained, and rethemed the look of the website
- 2.) SM Supermall Online Shop a version of Speedregalo website intended for SM online shopping. Rethemed and maintained the overall look of the website
- 3.) Booking Monitoring Web App develop from native PHP for monitoring booking and pickup
- 4.) Manifest Monitoring Web App develop from native PHP for monitoring manifests

COLLEGE THESIS

Classroom Management System (June 2017 – August 2017)

A web-based system that aims to organize the records and lectures of the students per subject. Developed using a php MVC framework (Codelgniter). The following modules of the thesis are:

- Attendance Management System
- Customizable Grading System
- Lecture Management
- Subjects and Semester Management
- Admin Dashboard, Students and Instructor Management

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- PHP
 - o Codelgniter Intermediate
 - o Laravel Beginner
 - Wordpress Beginner
 - Native PHP
- Javascript
 - Jauery Intermediate
 - VeuJs Beginner
 - Native Javascript
- Responsive Web Design / UI / UX
- HTML5 / CSS3 / SASS / SCSS
- Code optimization/standardization & SEO
- MySQL / MSSQL / Apache Server
- API Development
- GIT / Version Control
- System Architecture / MVC

SEMINARS/WORKSHOPS/TRAININGS ATTENDED

SAP Business One Info Session

May 2017

SAP Office, NAC Tower, Taguig City

CTI Summit 2017 (Machine Learning)

March 2017

Makati Diamond Hotel

PLDT Moveit Buildit VitroDataCenter

March 2017

Samsung Hall SM Aura, Manila

PLDT Online Thursdays

February 2017

Manila Marriott Hotel

AREN Computer Services

Seminar of Internet of Things, Cloud Computing, Ubiquitous Computing, Cisco Certifications, Android Programming and Robotics November 2016 – January 2017 Morayta St, Sampaloc, Manila

EDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND

Tertiary: Divine Word College of Calapan

Governor Infantado, Calapan, Oriental Mindoro

Secondary: Clarendon College

Roxas, Oriental Mindoro

Primary: Clarendon College

Roxas, Oriental Mindoro